http://vandewallecandies.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Caramel Corn & Popcorn
Chocolate Liqueur Cups (shot glasses)
Store Terms
This privacy policy is intended for all users of Vande Walle's Candies Inc. (vandewallescandies.com).
Vande Walle's Candies Inc. is dedicated to respecting and protecting the privacy of our clients. All information you provide, such as E-mail addresses or any additional personal information on or through any forms found on our site, will be used solely to support your relationship with Vande Walle's Candies Inc.. We strive to develop innovative methods to better serve our users. Our services are designed and operate with the protection of your privacy in mind. This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use Vande Walle's Candies Inc.'s services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it.
By visiting this web site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.
This privacy policy addresses the following areas:
What personally identifiable information Vande Walle's Candies Inc. collects.
What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the web site.
What organization collects the information.
How Vande Walle's Candies Inc. uses the information.
With whom Vande Walle's Candies Inc. may share user information.
What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the control of Vande Walle's Candies Inc.
How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Vande Walle's Candies Inc. at info@vandewallescandies.com. Any violation of this privacy policy will lead to suspension of user privileges and permanent removal from access to this web site.
Information Collection
Vande Walle Candies Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on our site. Vande Walle's Candies Inc. collects and monitors information from our users at several different points on our web site.
Registration
In order to use the services offered on our web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to disclose contact information (such as name and email address). If offered, it is optional for the user to disclose demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as a username). We do encourage full disclosure of these details in order for Vande Walle's Candies Inc. to provide a more customized experience on our site.
While Vande Walle's Candies Inc. exercises all due caution to protect your privacy, Vande Walle's Candies Inc. will not be held responsible for parties who attempt to illegally access our web site and intercept or access transmissions or private communications.
Unless described otherwise in this privacy policy, Vande Walle's Candies Inc. will not sell any information. All information collected by Vande Walle's Candies Inc. will be used solely by Vande Walle's Candies Inc. to deliver targeted newsletters and advertisements.
Information Use - "Profiles"
Vande Walle's Candies Inc. stores information collected through cookies, log files and/or third interests in your user profile. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users detailing specific viewing preferences. Subsequently, this collected information is linked to user's personally identifiable information,which provides directs pertinent marketing promotions to you and helps us improve site content for the user. Vande Walle's Candies Inc. does not share your profile with other third parties, unless specifically mentioned elsewhere in this policy.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Cookies, if used, will be used on Vande Walle's Candies Inc. to remember and recall login names, login information, previous purchases, potential purchases, as well as other items to help us better understand user's needs. By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use Vande Walle's Candies Inc.. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. For more details, see the above "Profile" section. We have no control over any third party that may also use cookies to store personal information. However, we do not provide this information to any third party.
Log Files
Like most standard web site servers we may use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, site administer, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Sharing
Legal Disclaimer:Though we exercise all due caution to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. This includes, but is not limited to, any defense to any claim in which Vande Walle's Candies Inc. is a defendant, to assist in any investigations by law enforcement agencies, or violations of any Vande Walle's Candies Inc. policy.
Aggregate Information (Non-Personally Identifiable)
While Vande Walle's Candies Inc. will not rent, sell or share your information in general, there are certain instances when your information may be used. Vande Walle's Candies Inc. does share aggregated demographic information and in some cases your e-mail address with others. This is how your information will be shared:
If Vande Walle's Candies Inc. merges with another company, this aggregate information will be shared with the merging company. These are the instances in which we will share user's personal information: As agreed to at the various sections under Vande Walle's Candies Inc.; Vande Walle's Candies Inc. does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except under the following circumstances:
We have your consent.
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf. When this is done, it is subject to agreements that oblige those parties to process such information only on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Vande Walle's Candies Inc. terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; We transfer or lease information about you if Vande Walle's Candies Inc. is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Vande Walle's Candies Inc. will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy; we do not support any illegal use of your private information and will make every effort to stop such practices in order to protect your privacy.
Business Transitions: In the event Vande Walle's Candies Inc.
goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, user's personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via e-mail, as well as with a prominent notice on our Web site for at least 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the user's personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.
Links
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Vande Walle's Candies Inc., are not responsible for the privacy practices of sites other than our own. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. Vande Walle's Candies Inc. may have co-branding and/or framing relations with other companies. In this case, you should be familiar with the privacy policies of both companies, since you may be subject to each of them.
Contacting Vande Walle's Candies Inc.: If you have questions or concerns about the Vande Walle's Candies Inc. guidelines, policies, procedures, you can contact us at info@vandewallescandies.com
Security
Notification of Changes: If we decide to change our privacy policy, changes will be posted to this privacy statement, our homepage, and other places we deem conspicuous and appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Vande Walle's Candies Inc. will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use user's personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, users will be notified via e-mail. Users will then be presented with a choice as to whether or not we become authorized to use their information in this different way. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users (who have opted to receive communications from Vande Walle's Candies Inc.), notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
Vande Walle's Candies Inc. and its affiliates maintain professional standards and have a high quality of respect to our members as well as our guest and affiliates
Follow us
Win Free Chocolates! Sign up for our Email Newsletter
